Beto提到，对于屏幕分辨率不同的手机应该使用分辨率不同的图标。
Beto mentioned that we should provide bit maps at different resolutions.
在我们的应用程序里，Nexus S使用了48 dib的图标，
In our app, the 48 dib icon on the Nexus S
虽然它看起来与Nexus 4甚至Nexus 5使用的图标大小一样。
looks to be about the same size as on the Nexus
但事实上，
4, and on the Nexus 5. However, in reality, this asset
相比于后两者，Nexus S显示的图标分辨率会更大一些。
that's being displayed is actually a lot bigger in terms of
为了证实这一点，
pixels compared to this one. To confirm, we can check out
我们不妨打开app资源文件夹来看一下。在drawable文件夹中，可以看到
the app resource folders. In the drawable folders, we see that
mdpi分辨率的设备中有一个像素为48x48的启动图标,
our app has a 48 by 48 pixel launcher icon for
它被放在mdpi分辨率的drawable文件夹中。
mdpi devices located in the drawable mdpi folder. To
对于屏幕分辨率更高的设备，若要达到同样令人满意的效果，
make an equivalent icon for the higher density devices,
我们需要一个像素更高的启动图标。
we need to make that icon progressively larger. To
那么，为了弄清这些图片究竟要多大，以及
know exactly how big to make these images and
如何将它们转换为像素更高的图片，
what the dibbed pixel conversion should be, we use
我们可以选择mdpi分辨率屏幕的设备作为一个基准。此时
an mdpi device as the baseline. This is where
一个dib相当于一个像素点。 然而在HDPI分辨率的
one dib equals one pixel. Then on the HDPI
设备上，一个dib则需被转化为1.5个像素点。
device one dib equals 1.5 pixels. And then it increases
同样的方法，对于xx HDPI分辨率的设备，
from there, all the way to an xx HDPI
一个dib等同于4个像素点。更多的换算，
device, where one dib equals four pixels. For more info
你可以参照以下的链接。
on the conversions, see the link below. Following those
按照这样的规律，我们可以一一对照分辨率不同的
rules, these are the sizes of the launcher icon in
drawable文件夹中的启动图标。MDPI分辨率的屏幕
our drawable folders. The MDPI one is 48 pixels
使用的图标像素为48x48。HDPI分辨率的屏幕使用的图标
by 48 pixels. The one for HDPI is 1.5 times
像素为1.5x48x48。    对于XHDPI分辨率的设备，
the size of this one. From an XHDPI device,
其图标像素是2x48x48。
the icon is two times the size of the MDPI
最后，对于XXHDPI分辨率的设备，其图标像素是3x48x48。
one, and for an XXHDPI device, the icon is the three times the size of this one.